<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
        <rss version='2.0'><channel>
        <title>Comments | scripture.sourceforge.net</title>
        <link>http://scripture.sourceforge.net</link>
        <description>scripture.sourceforge.net Feeds</description>
        <language>en-us</language><item>
            <title>one king: Jesus</title>
            <link>http://scripture.sourceforge.net?forum&amp;nid=141</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<a href="/?s=ACT+4%3A26">ACT 4:26</a> The kings of the earth stood up, and the rulers were gathered together against the Lord, and against his Christ.
27 For of a truth against thy holy child Jesus, whom thou hast anointed, both Herod, and Pontius Pilate, with the Gentiles, and the people of Israel, were gathered together 

<a href="/?s=ACT+17%3A7">ACT 17:7</a> Whom Jason hath received: and these all do contrary to the decrees of Caesar, saying that there is another king, [one] Jesus.<p></p>By uid[1]]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2012 15:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
            <category>ct</category>
            </item><item>
            <title>Small Script</title>
            <link>http://scripture.sourceforge.net?forum&amp;nid=138</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>
	This script sets links automatically, so you don&#39;t have to in nodes.<br />
	I suggest not having anything named like &quot;1 co 3&quot; or &quot;1 co 3:1&quot; but rather &quot;1co 3&quot; and &quot;<a href="/?s=%3B1co+3%3A1">;1co 3:1</a>&quot;.<br />
	<br />
	If your a windows user, <a href="/Mindmap/scripts/setlinks.groovy">upload this file</a> into &quot;C:/Program Files/Freeplane/scripts&quot; and restart freeplane.<br />
	<br />
	Now you will find it under tools&rarr;scripts. You can also create hotkeys for this purpose.<br />
	<br />
	Inserting links is very simple also if you use ctrl or shift in order to select all your nodes that you wish to convert into a link.</p>
<p></p>By uid[1]]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2012 21:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
            <category>ct</category>
            </item><item>
            <title>Artikler som beskriver agendaer til bibelselskapet og norsk-bibel</title>
            <link>http://scripture.sourceforge.net?forum&amp;nid=86</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<p> <a href="http://www.undermytree.net/BUP-artikler.html">http://www.undermytree.net/BUP-artikler.html</a></p> <p></p>By uid[1]]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 20:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
            <category>ct</category>
            </item><item>
            <title>New search capability</title>
            <link>http://scripture.sourceforge.net?forum&amp;nid=108</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The newest feature is t: which represents "these words".
Appart from the other "this order"; this will make it possible to search order-less.<p></p>By uid[1]]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2012 20:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
            <category>ct</category>
            </item><item>
            <title>Moved</title>
            <link>http://scripture.sourceforge.net?forum&amp;nid=99</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Due to lack of positive insights, this is now moved lower in bid priority.

AHRC promote agenda directed translations such as RSV while using meaningless arguments to demote the more living translations.

Further research is required.<p></p>By uid[1]]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 21:23:04 +0000</pubDate>
            <category>ct</category>
            </item><item>
            <title>Are we then to put other men in front?</title>
            <link>http://scripture.sourceforge.net?forum&amp;nid=95</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Transitional//EN" "http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-transitional.dtd">
<html>
<head>
</head>
<body>
<p>1PE 2:13 [THE CHRISTIAN AND THE STATE] Submit yourselves to every ordinance of man for the Lord&#39s sake: whether it be to the king, as supreme;<br />14 Or unto governors, as unto them that are sent by him for the punishment of evildoers, and for the praise of them that do well.<br />15 For so is the will of God, that with well doing ye may put to silence the ignorance of foolish men:<br />16 As free, and not using [your] liberty for a cloke of maliciousness, but as the servants of God.<br />17 Honour all [men]. Love the brotherhood. Fear God. Honour the king.<br /><br /><a href="/?s=JHN+19%3A11">JHN 19:11</a> Jesus answered, Thou couldest have no power [at all] against me, except it were given thee from above: therefore he that delivered me unto thee hath the greater sin. <br /><br />1PE 1:11 Searching what, or what manner of time the Spirit of Christ which was in them did signify, when it testified beforehand the sufferings of Christ, and the glory that should follow. <br /><br />1PE 2:20 For what glory [is it], if, when ye be buffeted for your faults, ye shall take it patiently? but if, when ye do well, and suffer [for it], ye take it patiently, this [is] acceptable with God. <br /><br /><a href="/?s=JAM+5%3A10">JAM 5:10</a> Take, my brethren, the prophets, who have spoken in the name of the Lord, for an example of suffering affliction, and of patience. <br /><br />Are we then to suffer the human authorities, submitting ourselves under them; even when they are not just. As long as we are not breaking Gods commandments?.<br /><br />The Lord let himself suffer, and be in subject to human authority; except when it was against the better.<br /><br />Are we then proclaim human laws? or as being Gods example; would it be against or for such?.<br /><br />What do Jesus say about it?.<br /><br /><a href="/?s=MAT+15%3A2">MAT 15:2</a> Why do thy disciples transgress the tradition of the elders? for they wash not their hands when they eat bread.<br />3 But he answered and said unto them, Why do ye also transgress the commandment of God by your tradition?<br />4 For God commanded, saying, Honour thy father and mother: and, He that curseth father or mother, let him die the death.<br />5 But ye say, Whosoever shall say to [his] father or [his] mother, [It is] a gift, by whatsoever thou mightest be profited by me;<br />6 And honour not his father or his mother, [he shall be free]. Thus have ye made the commandment of God of none effect by your tradition.<br />7 [Ye] hypocrites, well did Esaias prophesy of you, saying<br />8 This people draweth nigh unto me with their mouth, and honoureth me with [their] lips; but their heart is far from me.<br />9 But in vain they do worship me, teaching [for] doctrines the commandments of men. <br /><br /><a href="/?s=MAT+19%3A30">MAT 19:30</a> But many [that are] first shall be last; and the last [shall be] first. <br /><br /></p>
</body>
</html><p></p>By uid[1]]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 22:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
            <category>ct</category>
            </item><item>
            <title>Rom 13</title>
            <link>http://scripture.sourceforge.net?forum&amp;nid=83</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<a href="/?s=ROM+13%3A1">ROM 13:1</a> μη♪ νικω♪ υπο♪ του♪ κακου♪ αλλα♪ νικα♪ εν♪ τω♪ αγαθω♪ το♪ κακον♪<br><a href="/?s=ROM+13%3A1">ROM 13:1</a> Let every soul be subject • unto the higher • powers. For there is • no power but of God: • the powers that be • are • ordained • of God. <br><br>higher<br>: ὑπερέχω<br>1) to have or hold over one<br>2) to stand out, rise above, overtop a) to be above, be superior in rank, authority, power<br>1) the prominent men, rulers b) to excel, to be superior, better than, to surpass<br>_wT: hyperechō<br><br>What power is better, what power is not the faith we have in the Lord. Whos place is not the Lords but the above. whats not the influence that we are to hold above. is it the traditions of men with their doctrines?. Or would it be the Lords.<br><br>Power<br>: ἐξουσία<br>1) power of choice, liberty of doing as one pleases a) leave or permission<br>2) physical and mental power a) the ability or strength with which one is endued, which he either possesses or exercises<br>3) the power of authority (influence) and of right (privilege)<br>4) the power of rule or government (the power of him whose will and commands must be submitted to by others and obeyed) a) universally<br>1) authority over mankind b) specifically<br>1) the power of judicial decisions<br>2) of authority to manage domestic affairs c) metonymically<br>1) a thing subject to authority or rule a) jurisdiction<br>2) one who possesses authority a) a ruler, a human magistrate b) the leading and more powerful among created beings superior to man, spiritual potentates d) a sign of the husband"s authority over his wife<br>1) the veil with which propriety required a women to cover herself e) the sign of regal authority, a crown<br>_wT: exousia<p></p>By uid[1]]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 23:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
            <category>ct</category>
            </item><item>
            <title>Laws of the pharicees</title>
            <link>http://scripture.sourceforge.net?forum&amp;nid=74</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ungodly judges give no room for wisdom and disciplination. Judging after imagenary farytales that"s not thaught either by force during transgression. Many laws are made impossible, and traps of the unwise is made in hidden councels. I"n disagreement with the wise. They are made to trap even the richeous of God. Snairs by wolfes in sheep  clothing are made to fill their own fleshy needs; either recognization, wealth, or other unwise experiment results to find any identification to own fallable ideas. Or imagenary ideas of control. Not giving heads to the cry of the needy or richeousness. Digging their own hole rejecting to move beyond their unwise socalled blessed rights. Judging after their own lusts, and ignorance. Not being aware of their own actions. They fall with their ditch. Their end will be sudden, but their feets fall low; the day our Lord returns. May the Lord be graceful. Yet they won"t find it. For they seek him not.<p></p>By uid[1]]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2011 19:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
            <category>ct</category>
            </item><item>
            <title>Question regarding Heb 13:17</title>
            <link>http://scripture.sourceforge.net?forum&amp;nid=67</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Transitional//EN" "http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-transitional.dtd">
<html>
<head>
</head>
<body>
<p><a href="/?s=Heb+13%3A17">Heb 13:17</a> Obeye the that have the oversight of you and submit youre selves to them for they watch for youre soules even as they that must geve a comptes: that they maye do it with ioye and not with grefe. For that is an vnproffitable thynge for you. (TNT)<br /><br />geneva, ylt, and tyndale; all have different way of saying this apart from kjv<br /><br />17|8 Be obedient to those leading you, and be subject, for these do watch for your souls, as about to give account, that with joy they may do this, and not sighing, for this [is] unprofitable to you.<br />17|9 Obey them that haue the ouersight of you, and submit your selues: for they watche for your soules, as they that must giue accountes, that they may doe it with ioy, and not with griefe: for that is vnprofitable for you. <br /><br />look at kjv:<br /><a href="/?s=Heb+13%3A17">Heb 13:17</a> Obey them that have the rule over you, and submit yourselves: for they watch for your souls, as they that must give account, that they may do it with joy, and not with grief: for that is unprofitable for you. (KJV)<br /><br />there is a very clear difference; here kjv was supposed to be based upon the combination of geneva and tyndale; yet errored<br />this might be a false teaching set in by king james himself<br />greek include "of Godliness", and not human rulers; atleast i wouldn"t say it dogmatically!.</p>
</body>
</html><p></p>By uid[1]]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2011 18:10:02 +0000</pubDate>
            <category>ct</category>
            </item><item>
            <title>Copies from various sites</title>
            <link>http://scripture.sourceforge.net?forum&amp;nid=65</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Would anyone like to take a look at several copies I"ve made of various major bible sites?. KJV, YLT...<p></p>By uid[1]]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 14:29:24 +0000</pubDate>
            <category>ct</category>
            </item></channel></rss>